const sampleQuestion = [
  {
    question: "It refers to a measure of position It refers to a measure of positionIt refers to a measure of position It refers to a measure of position It refers to a measure of positionIt refers to a measure of position It refers to a measure of position It refers to a measure of position It refers to a measure of position It refers to a measure of position It refers to a measure of position It refers to a measure of position It refers to a measure of position", 
    answers: [
      "Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile",
      "Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile",
      "Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile",
      "Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile Quartile"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0
  },
  {
    question: "It refers to a measure of position which divides the distribution into 10 parts", 
    answers: [
      "Quartile",
      "Decile",
      "Percentile",
      "Range"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the equivalent percentile of the upper quartile", 
    answers: [
      "25th Percentile (ùëÉ25)",
      "50th Percentile (ùëÉ50)",
      "75th Percentile (ùëÉ75)",
      "All of these"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2
  },
  {
    question: "What percentile is equal to the 1st decile", 
    answers: [
      "10th Percentile (ùëÉ10)",
      "20th Percentile (ùëÉ20)",
      "30th Percentile (ùëÉ30)",
      "40th Percentile ((ùëÉ40)"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0
  },
  {
    question: "In a certain shopping mall, restaurants charge P140, P195, P125, P150, P200, P165, P175, P230, and P180 for a regular dinner. \n \n What is the value of the 25th percentile in the given data set", 
    answers: [
      "P145 ",
      "P175",
      "P195",
      "P225"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following statements is true?", 
    answers: [
      "PùëÉ50 = ùê∑2",
      "ùëÉ25 = ùê∑2",
      "ùëÉ20 = ùê∑2",
      "ùëÉ10 = ùê∑2"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2
  },
  {
    question: "It is a positional measure that divides a set of data into ten equal parts", 
    answers: [
      "Decile",
      "Percentile",
      "Quartile",
      "Quantile"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0
  },
  {
    question: "Nina got a score of 55 which is equivalent to 70th Percentile in a Statistics test. Which of the following is not true", 
    answers: [
      "She scored above 70% of her classmates",
      "Thirty percent of the class got scores of 55 and above",
      "If the passing mark is the first quartile, she passed the test",
      "Her score is below the 5th decile"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3
  },
  {
    question: "The 3rd quartile of the ages of 100 Grade 10 students is 16 years old. Which of the following statements is true", 
    answers: [
      "Twenty students are 16 years old",
      "Most of the students are above 16 years old",
      "Twenty-five percent of the students are 16 years old and above",
      "Seventy-five percent of the students are 16 years old and above"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2
  },
  {
    question: "The first grading grades in Algebra of selected students are the following: \n 75 76 78 80 81 81 84 85 88 89 89. \n \n What is the percentile rank of 88", 
    answers: [
      "52.73%",
      "62.73%",
      "72.73",
      " 82.73"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2
  },
  {
    question: "The following are the Midterm scores of selected Senior High School students in a 100 ‚Äì item test: \n 82, 45, 37, 98, 100, 74, 87, 89, 63, 76, 75, 61, 43, 99. \n \n The midterm score of 45 is the _____ decile", 
    answers: [
      "1st",
      "2nd ",
      "3rd",
      "4th"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1
  },
  {
    question: "The following are the Midterm scores of selected Senior High School students in a 100 ‚Äì item test: \n  82, 45, 37, 98, 100, 74, 87, 89, 63, 76, 75, 61, 43, 99. \n \n The percentile ranking of 61 is _____ percent", 
    answers: [
      "21.43",
      "31.43",
      "41.43",
      "51.43"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0
  },
];
  
export default sampleQuestion;